So I really want the people on the table now to say,
所以我真的希望现在在桌子上的人能说
"Here, your hand, open it a little more to the left.
“看，你的手，再向左边打开一点。
Here, move back a little like..."
看，稍微退后一点，就像……”
Get in touch with the room around you.
与你周围的空间建立联系。
Get into this perception as if your fingers are lengthening.
让自己完全沉浸在这种感知中，仿佛你的手指在伸长。
Take the whole body.
感受整个身体。
Observe the breathing.
观察呼吸。
Become aware of the breath of life.
感受生命之息。
The breath that moves.
流动的呼吸。
And also, keep your eyes open and feel...
同时，睁开眼睛，感受……
this kind of stillness
那种静止
in the room
在房间里
stay open
保持开放
and perceive this kind of stillness
并感知那种静止
in the room
在房间里
the breath of life
生命之息
the breathing
呼吸
and the stillness
和静止
are present in the room
都存在于房间里
when these three elements
当这三个元素
manifest themselves
显现时
They will take care of you.
它们会照顾你。
The breath of life.
生命之息。
The breath of life is this life force, it's the life you have in your hands.
生命之息，就是这种生命力，就是你手中所拥有的生命。
Breathing is what moves, inhale and exhale.
呼吸，就是那种运动，吸气和呼气。
And then there's the space around you, this space, this
然后是你周围的空间，这个空间，这种
stillness.
静止。
Try to allow yourself
试着让自己被治疗过程所
to be encompassed by a therapeutic process and to
包围，并让自己
allow yourself to heal.
得到疗愈。
The breath is there.
呼吸就在那里。
You feel it.
你感受得到。
You can feel the diaphragm moving.
你可以感受到膈肌在运动。
Don't try to influence it.
不要试图去影响。
Observe.
观察。
The breath itself has a fulcrum.
呼吸本身有一个支点。
It's like a door opening.
就像一扇门打开。
There's a door closing.
有一扇门关闭。
A door opening.
一扇门打开。
The breath of life.
生命之息。
The breath that moves.
流动的呼吸。
The silence.
寂静。
and the crystalline stillness of the room.
和房间水晶般的静止。
Try to perceive this tranquility.
试着去感受这份宁静。
The breath has its fulcrum.
呼吸有它的支点。
It's like a door that opens and closes.
它就像一扇门，开开合合。
There's a hinge.
有一个铰链。
Just try to perceive this hinge that...
试着去感受这个铰链，它...
opens, which becomes a fulcrum.
打开，成为一个支点。
It's almost a still point in the breath.
这几乎是呼吸的一个静止点。
The door opens, the door closes. And you will gradually
门开了，门关了。你将一点点地进入
move into the sensation of the
对这个支点的感觉和
perception of this fulcrum, while being aware of the breath of
感知，同时意识到生命之息。
life. It's the living body.
这是活生生的身体。
that you have in your hand, this life force that it has, the
你手中握着的，它所拥有的生命力量，
breath, the space
呼吸，你周围的
around you, the space behind you, the space above you, the contacts
空间，你身后的空间，你上方的空间，与大地的接触，
with the earth, the different zones, A, B, C,
不同的区域，A、B、C、
D, which open around you, finally
D，在你周围展开，最终
the breath a little, it's like a panel.
呼吸有点像一个面板。
with a fixed point above. There is the dynamic
上面有一个固定点。有动态的
silence, the stillness,
寂静，静止，
as if this tranquility, this stillness, this
仿佛这份宁静，这份静止，这个
point merged.
点融合在一起。
Imagine you are in an ocean of tranquility.
想象你置身于一片宁静的海洋中。
You will feel a warmth now.
你现在会感觉到一股暖意。
It's as if you have this ability to increase your perception to the horizon.
这就像你拥有将你的感知扩展到地平线的能力。
You are moving into zone D.
你进入D区。
You are sitting in an ocean of tranquility.
你坐在一片宁静的海洋中。
And the breath...
而呼吸...
of life, the breath, the
生命之息，呼吸，
stillness, then
静止，然后
there is the median line, then from the median line,
有中线，然后从中线，
there is like from the median line to the horizon, then
仿佛从中线到地平线，然后
there is a wave.
有一波浪。
from the horizon, like
从地平线，就像
a wave coming from the horizon towards
一股波浪从地平线涌向
the median line and which
中线，它将你
puts you back in perfect time, let this
带回到完美的时间，让它到来。
wave come, for therapists be
波浪，对于治疗师来说，请
well in
站稳
your feet, the body's warmth
脚跟，身体的温度
grows. It's like a
升高。这就像一种
homogeneity. A little
同质性。有点
like when all these elements harmonize,
像所有这些元素和谐共处时，
you can feel the breath coming from the horizon, a little
你可以感觉到呼吸从地平线传来，有点
like the wind moves in the air.
像风在空气中移动。
You have a feeling of globality, of homogeneity,
你有一种整体感、同质感、
of calm, of well-being.
平静感、幸福感。
You can withdraw and then exchange.
你可以退出，然后进行交流。
Subtitling ST' 501
字幕 ST' 501